Register of the Christopher Temple Emmet Papers 1913-1974
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1935-1974
  - Deak, Francis, 1957
  - Dean, Arthur H., 1955-1957
  - Debevoise, Eli Whitney, 1961
  - Decter, Moshe, 1954-1970
  - Deeken, Hans-Werner, 1962-1963
  - Deharde, Martha, 1967
  - Delgado, Ambassador Francisco A., 1959-1961
  - Delgado, Mucio, 1959-1965
  - Dembinski, Jan, 1944
  - Dempsey, Governor John, 1970
  - Denby, Charles, 1966
  - Denny, George V., Jr., 1938-1947
  - Dent (J. M.) & Sons, 1947
  - Denzer, Mrs. Bernard, 1946-1947
  - De Rochefort, Nicholas, 1957-1959
  - De Rochemont, Richard, 1943-1947
  - Derwinski, Representative Edward J., 1963
  - De Simone, Jack, 1963
  - Desvernine, Raoul E., 1946
  - De Toledano, Ralph, 1946-1967
  - De Vegh, Imre, 1957-1960
  - Devine, J. Dudley, 1958-1960
  - Dewey, John, 1946
  - Dewey, Governor Thomas E., 1947-1962
  - Dexter, Byron, 1951
  - Diamond, Martin, 1957
  - Diebold, John, 1968-1973
  - Diebold, William, Jr., 1961-1972
  - Diederich, Hunt, 1947
  - Diem, Ambassador Bo, 1967
  - Diem, President Ngo Dinh, 1951-1957
  - Diggs, Representative Charles C., Jr., 1959-1969
  - Dimitrov, George M., 1947-1972
  - Dingell, Representative John D., 1967-1969
  - Dinnebeil, Martha, 1947
  - Dirksen, Senator Everett McKinley, 1964
  - Disgne, Jill S., undated
  - Disney, Walt, 1959
  - Dixon, Ambassador Sir Pierson, 1959
  - Dobriansky, Lev E., 1960-1965
  - Docheff, Ivan, 1965
  - Docking, Governor Robert, 1970
  - Dodd, Grace (Mrs. Thomas J.), undated
  - Dodd, Senator Thomas J., 1956-1971
  - Doelger, Mrs, Carl, 1947
  - Doenhoff, Countess Marion, 1951-1973 (Box 70)
  - Doering, O. C., Jr., 1960-1963
  - Doering, Mrs. O. C., 1960
  - Doherty, Edward, 1970
  - Doherty, George, 1946-1965
  - Dohrn, Christopher, 1956
  - Dohrn, Klaus, 1946-1970
  - Domes, Alfred, 1962-1973
  - Dominick, Senator Peter H., 1963-1971
  - Donnell, Senator Forrest C., 1945
  - Donohue, Representative Harold D., 1967-1969
  - Donovan, Reverend Vincent, 1947
  - Donovan, General William J., 1946-1957
  - Dooley, Dr. Thomas E., 1959
  - Dorn, Representative William Jennings Bryan, 1967
  - Dos Passos, John, 1961-1968
  - Dougherty, James E., 1971
  - Douglas, Donald W., 1959
  - Douglas, Lewis W., 1941-1947
  - Douglas, Senator Paul H., 1939-1973 (Box 71)
  - Douglas-Hamilton, Lord Malcolm, 1956
  - Douglas-Hamilton, Lady Natalie (Lady Malcolm), 1946-1972
  - Dow, Harold B., 1957
  - Dowling, Eddie, 1946
  - Downey, Roger, 1967
  - Downey, Senator Sheridan, 1945
  - Downing, Representative Thomas N., 1969
  - Downs, Alyce M., 1946
  - Doyle, Frank D., 1960-1961
  - Draper, Mrs., 1946
  - Drayton, William Astor, 1946
  - Drechsler, Guenther K., 1966
  - Dreier, Alex, 1961
  - Drew, J. E., 1959
  - Driscoll, Catherine A., 1959
  - Drucker, Robert F., 1967
  - Drum, Barbara, 1958
  - Drum, John F. T., 1949
  - Drummond, Roscoe, 1956-1973
  - Dubinsky, David, 1941-1964
  - Duchich, Mitchell M., 1946
  - Dudley, Alan, 1940-1941
  - Duff, Father Edward, 1950-1956
  - Duffus, R. L., 1959
  - Duke, Ambassador Angier Biddle, 1956-1973 (Box 72)
  - Dulles, Allen W., 1947-1966
  - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing, 1958
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1947-1958
  - Dunn, Gano, 1946
  - Dunner, Joseph, 1949-1970
  - Dupuis, Gratia, 1967
  - Durholz, Otto B., 1947
  - Durkee, William P., 1969-1972
  - Dushnyck, Walter, 1948-1972
  - Dutton, Frederick G., 1963-1964
  - Dworshak, Senator Henry C., 1956
  - Dwyer, William M., 1960
  - Eagleton, Senator Thomas F., 1969
  - Earle, Edward Mead, 1949
  - Eastland, Senator James O., 1959-1969
  - Eastman, Eliena (Mrs. Max), 1946
  - Eastman, Max, 1954-1966
  - Easton, Edward R., 1955-1956
  - Eban, Ambassador Abba, 1958
  - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1947
  - Eckardt, Felix von, 1968
  - Eckardt, Wolfgang von, 1947-1954
  - Eckhardt, Tibor, 1949-1969
  - Ecsay, Laszlo, 1950
  - Edison, Governor Charles, 1954-1959
  - Edmondson, D'Arcy, 1947-1955
  - Egan, Governor William A., 1965
  - Eichelberger, Clark, 1939-1940
  - Eisenhower, President Dwight D., 1955-1964
  - Eisner, J. Lester, 1940
  - Elbau, Julius, 1945
  - Eliasberg, Mrs. George, 1952
  - Eliot, Major George Fielding, 1945-1950
  - Elkinton, Howard W., 1955
  - Ellingston, John, 1940
  - Elliott, Eleanor, 1967
  - Elliott, William Yandell, 1947-1953
  - Ellis, Betty, 1951-1970
  - Ellis, Monsignor John Tracy, 1959
  - Ellison, Fanny, 1960
  - Ellsworth, Mary Louise (Mrs. Lincoln), 1947
  - Emeny, Brooks, 1948
  - Emerson, William, 1941
  - Emmet, Alida Chanler (Mrs. Christopher T., Sr.), 1947
  - Emmet, Christopher T., Sr., 1943-1947
  - Emmet, Mrs. Grenville, 1947
  - Emmet, Thomas A., 1947-1970
  - Emmet, Winthrop S., 1939-1958
  - Engel, Irving M., 1950-1970
  - Engel, Mrs. Irving M., 1949-1950
  - Engen, Ambassador Hans, 1958
  - Enger, Jane, 1970
  - Engle, Senator Clair, 1959-1963
  - Ensher, Angin, 1964
  - Enthoven, Alain C., 1968
  - Eppstein, John, 1959
  - Epstein, Julius, 1945-1959 (Box 73)
  - Epstein, Klaus, 1967
  - Epstein, M. R., 1940
  - Eren, Nuri, 1957
  - Erhard, Ludwig, 1968
  - Erickson, Betty, 1963
  - Erlanger, Benjamin F., 1940
  - Erlanger, Sydney B., 1940
  - Erler, Fritz, 1963-1966
  - Ernestine, Mathilde, 1968
  - Ernst, Morris L., 1944-1949
  - Ervin, Senator Sam, Jr., 1969
  - Esin, Ambassador M. Seyfullah, 1959
  - Estabrook, Robert H., 1958
  - Evans, Miss, 1971
  - Evans, Sir Francis, 1946
  - Evans, Roger F., 1946
  - Evening Standard (London), 1947
  - Everett, John R., 1973
  - Eversole, Henry, 1946
  - Fabian, Bela, 1950-1960
  - Fabregat, Ambassador Enrique Rodriquez, 1957
  - Fackenthal, Frank D., 1948
  - Fadiman, Clifton, 1949
  - Fairchild, Henry Pratt, 1949
  - Falk, Regina J., 1947
  - Falkenhausen, Baron Gotthard von, 1952-1970
  - Falkowski, Edward, 1962
  - Farber, Barry, 1964-966
  - Farley, James A., 1946-1965
  - Farmer, Dorothy, 1957-1959
  - Farmer, Gene, 1956
  - Farnsworth, Miss, 1939
  - Farrell, James T., 1949-1957
  - Faulkner, Alex, 1945-1956
  - Faulkner, William, 1960
  - Feddersen, Donley F., 1946
  - Federer, Georg, 1962-1964
  - Feely, Father Raymond T., 1941
  - Feighan, Representative Michael T., 1957-1961
  - Feinberg, Israel, 1947
  - Felknor, Bruce L., 1961-1962
  - Felknor, Rhea, 1966
  - Fennell, Francis, 1954
  - Ferger, Roger H., 1958
  - Ferguson, Judge Homer, 1958
  - Fermi, Enrico, 1949
  - Ferrero, Frank, Jr., 1965
  - Ferriday, Caroline, 1961
  - Fesino, Nataly, 1949
  - Fetter, Joseph, 1946
  - Fidler, Nevin, 1959
  - Field, George, 1941-1970
  - Field, Marshall, 1941-1964 (Box 74)
  - Field, Mrs. Marshall, 1946
  - Finch, Kip, 1953
  - Findley, Representative Paul, 1965-1968
  - Finkelstein, Louis, 1944-1949
  - Finkelstein, M. I., 1939
  - Finletter, Gretchen (Mrs. Thomas K.), 1947
  - Finletter, Thomas K., 1941-1966
  - Finley, Mrs. John, 1957
  - Finn, Agnes, 1957
  - Finucane, James, 1948-1953
  - Firbank, Giles, 1962
  - Fircks, Baron Otto von, 1972
  - Fireside Press, 1946
  - Fischer, John, 1960
  - Fischer, Louis, 1945-1950
  - Fischer, Richard D., 1966
  - Fischer, Ruth, 1946
  - Fishel, Wesley, 1965
  - Fisher, John M., 1966-1973
  - Fisher, Mitchell Salem, 1939
  - Fisk University, 1947
  - Fiszman, Joseph R., 1953
  - Fitch, George A., 1946-1952
  - Fitch, Geraldine Townsend (Mrs. George A.), 1944-1969
  - Fitch, W. C., 1946
  - Fitelson, H. William, 1957-1959
  - Flaherty, Father Daniel L., 1962-1970
  - Flanders, Senator Ralph L., 1959
  - Flechner, Max H., 1959
  - Fletcher, M. C., 1959
  - Fluegelman, Arthur, 1940
  - Flynt, Ralph C. M., 1956
  - Focke, Katherina, 1973
  - Fogler, R. H., 1946
  - Foley, William E., 1950
  - Fong, Senator Hiram, 1969
  - Fonteine, L. E., 1965
  - Ford, Representative Gerald R., 1959-1970
  - Ford, Henry, II, 1960-1964
  - Ford, I. John (?), 1946
  - Ford, John, 1959
  - Fordham University, 1947
  - Forell, Reverend F. J., 1958
  - Fornia, Lawrence M., 1957
  - Forsch, Frederick D., 1968
  - Forsling, Betty, 1957
  - Forster, Arnold, 1957-1967
  - Forster, Clifford, 1961
  - Forster, Monsignor Karl, 1964-1967
  - Forthmann, Heinz, 1952
  - Foschini, Father Bernard M., 1957
  - Fosdick, Dorothy, 1967
  - Fosdick, Reverend Harry Emerson, 1944-1946
  - Foster, Cedric, 1958-1961
  - Foster, Clifford, 1950
  - Foster, J. F., 1962
  - Fotich, Constantine, 1957
  - Fourie, Ambassador Bernardus Gerhardus, 1959
  - Fox, Yolande, 1960
  - France, Conseiller Cultural, New York, 1946
  - France Forever, 1945-1946
  - Franklin, George S., Jr., 1950-1970
  - Franklin, General John M., 1953
  - Frary, William T., 1947
  - Frederick, Pauline, 1958
  - Fredland, Edmund, 1962
  - Freedman, Blanch, 1946
  - Freedman, Emanuel, 1958
  - Freedman, George, 1965
  - Freedman, Paul Warren, 1958
  - Freelander, Ronald, 1958 (Box 75)
  - Freeman, Mansfield, 1952-1959
  - Freer, Evelyn L., 1946
  - Freitas, Geoffrey de, 1966
  - Fremd, Donald N., 1958
  - French Broadcast System, 1963
  - French Press and Information Service, 1946
  - Freud, Arthur, 1947
  - Freund, Mr., 1958
  - Frey, J. H., 1949
  - Friedheim, Jerry W., 1968-1970
  - Friedlaender, Ernst, 1953-1958
  - Friedman, Isabel T., 1956
  - Friedrich, Carl J., 1940-1964
  - Friedrich, Mila, 1946
  - Friedrich, Otto, 1964
  - Friendly, Alfred, 1958
  - Fritchen, Dean, 1960
  - Fritchey, Clayton, 1963
  - Frohlich, Hans, 1946-1971
  - Fry, Reverend Franklin Clark, 1960
  - Fry, Varian, 1944-1946
  - Fuchs, Mr., 1944
  - Fulbright, Senator J. W., 1959-1960
  - Fulton, Representative James G., 1957
  - Fulton Trust Company, 1940-1947
  - Furman, Norman, 1965
  - Furstenwalde, H. C., 1948-1950
  - Fybish, Ira, 1966
  - Gabriel Silver Lecture Committee, 1954
  - Gadomski, Feliks, 1966-1973
  - Gaertner, Hermann W., 1957
  - Gafenco, Gregoire, 1949
  - Gaitskell, Hugh, 1954
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1948-1958
  - Gallagher, James J., 1966
  - Galligan, John Paul, 1966
  - Gallo, Gregory M., 1965
  - Galpin, Perrin C., 1960
  - Gammell, Valentine, 1947
  - Gannon, Father Robert I., 1944-1960
  - Gapp, F. W., 1959
  - Gard, Colonel Robert, 1971
  - Garden, Gordon, 1946
  - Gardiner, Father Harold C., 1957-1962
  - Gardiner, John P., 1956-1959
  - Gardner, Clinton C., 1952-1954
  - Gardony, Frank, 1958
  - Garfinkel, Barry, 1947-1948
  - Garin, Ambassador Vasco Vieira, 1958
  - Garrison, Lloyd K., 1938-1960
  - Garside, Dr. B. A., 1943-1973
  - Gaspar, Edmund, 1961-1965
  - Gates, Thomas S., Jr., 1960
  - Gauss, Christian, 1947
  - Gavin, General James M., 1958-1960
  - Gavrilovic, Milan, 1955
  - Gelder, Stuart, 1947
  - Gelston, Robert, 1957
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1957
  - George, Manfred, 1950-1962
  - Gerard, Mrs. James W., 1970
  - Germenji, Vasil, 1965
  - Gerstenfeld, Rabbi Norman, 1957-1960
  - Gibbons, Father William J., 1945-1949
  - Gibian, Mrs. Richard, 1950
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1945-1947
  - Gideonse, Harry D., 1944-1973
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia C., 1947 (Box 76)
  - Gildner, Jay W., 1959
  - Gillam, Dorothy, 1939
  - Gingras, Angele de T., 1957-1971
  - Girard, Blanche, 1942
  - Girard, Robert, 1962-1965
  - Gladstone, Milton S., 1972
  - Gleason, James, 1956
  - Gleason, Thomas W., 1964
  - Glenn, Miss, 1947
  - Glickman, Marty, 1946
  - Globke, Hans, 1968-1973
  - Glynn, Doyle, 1946
  - Goergy, Laszlo, 1970
  - Goff, Marion, 1944-1947
  - Goldberg, Rabbi Joshua L., 1962
  - Goldberg, Max, 1966
  - Goldbloom, Maurice J., 1947-1955
  - Golden, Harry, 1961
  - Goldman, George S., 1940
  - Goldsborough, Charles R., Jr., 1961
  - Goldsmith, Arthur J., 1940-1960
  - Goldsmith, Lawrence L., 1940
  - Goldsmith, Richard, 1940
  - Goldstein, Rabbi Israel, 1954
  - Goldwater, Senator Barry, 1959-1969
  - Gollancz, Victor, 1948
  - Gomory, Andrew, 1950
  - Gong, Walter, 1958
  - Goodell, Senator Charles E., 1969
  - Goodkind, Howard, 1946
  - Goodman, Edward, 1941
  - Goodman, Nena M., 1965
  - Goold-Adams, Richard, 1959
  - Gordon, Edmund von, 1958
  - Gore, Senator Albert, 1959-1960
  - Gorin, Captain Serge de, 1956
  - Goris, Jan-Albert, 1947
  - Gorman, Patrick E., 1959
  - Gorman, Thomas K., 1961
  - Gotham Hotel, 1946
  - Gotshal, Sylvan, 1953
  - Gould, James L., 1967
  - Goulding, Jane, 1946-1947
  - Gourevitch, Gregoire, 1949
  - Grace, Charles R., 1951-1960
  - Grace, J. Peter, 1958-1960
  - Gradl, Johann-Baptist, 1966
  - Graevenitz, Dr. Alexander von, 1966-1967
  - Graf, William B., 1950
  - Graff, D. R., 1959
  - Grafton, Samuel, 1940-1943
  - Graham, Senator Frank P., 1939-1947
  - Graham, Father Robert A., 1959-1963
  - Gramont, Sanche de, 1961
  - Grant, Alan G., Jr., 1960-1964
  - Graphic Arts Forum, 1939
  - Gravel, Senator Mike, 1969
  - Gray, Barry, 1962-1969
  - Gray, Kenneth E., 1970
  - Gray, Mrs. Yolan, 1957
  - Green, Charles E., 1958
  - Green, John, 1947
  - Green, Mary, 1955
  - Green, William, 1939-1950
  - Greenbaum, Joseph J., 1971-1972
  - Greenbie, Sidney, 1945
  - Greene, Edward P., Jr., 1939
  - Greenleigh, Arthur, 1952
  - Greer, James E., 1946
  - Greeshamer, Mrs. C., 1947
  - Grew, Ambassador Joseph C., 1945-1956
  - Grewe, Ambassador Wilhelm, 1959-1961
  - Griessemer, Tom, 1946
  - Griffing, A. W., 1940
  - Griffith, Sanford, 1940-1950
  - Griffith, Thomas, 1956-1962
  - Griffith, William E., 1951-1971
  - Griffiths, Monsignor James, 1947
  - Groedel, Dr. Franz, 1950
  - Gross, Ernest A., 1950-1972
  - Gruenfeld, Herbert, 1973 (Box 77)
  - Gruenther, General Alfred M., 1968
  - Grunewald, Ch., 1946
  - Gruson, Sydney, 1966
  - Gubbrud, Governor Archie, 1961
  - Guinzburg, Harold K., 1949
  - Guradze, Heinz, 1947
  - Gurian, Waldemar, 1952
  - Gurland, A. R. L., 1958
  - Gurney, Senator Chan, 1948
  - Gurock, William B., 1949
  - Gutman, Eleanor B., 1940
  - Gutowski, Mr., 1944
  - Guttenberg, Baroness Elizabeth von und zu, 1948-1973
  - Guttenberg, Baron Karl Theodor von und zu, 1959-1971
  - Guttenberg, Baroness Rosl von und zu, 1973
  - Gwinn, Representative Ralph W., 1946
  - Haagse Post, 1956
  - Haentzschele, Wilfred, 1971
  - Hagard, John, 1957
  - Hahn, Emily, 1944-1956
  - Hahn, Kurt, 1955
  - Hahn, Peter, 1963-1966
  - Hahn, Walter F., 1960-1972
  - Halberstadt, Marion, 1940
  - Halecki, Oscar, 1944
  - Halemba, Rosa M., 1947
  - Halifax, Ambassador Viscount, 1944
  - Halleck, Representative Charles A., 1960-1963
  - Hallett, George, 1945
  - Halpern, Representative Seymour, 1967
  - Halstead, J. G. H., 1960
  - Hamilton, Mary Agnes, 1950
  - Hamilton, Thomas J., 1961
  - Hammarskjold, Dag, 1956-1958
  - Hammerstein, Oscar, II, 1949
  - Han, Li Wu, 1952
  - Hanighan, Frank C., 1947
  - Hannegan, Robert, undated
  - Hannemann, William J. F., 1962
  - Hansen, Robert W., 1961
  - Hanstein, George, 1949-1955
  - Hard, William, 1945
  - Harding, M. H., 1944
  - Harding, Mrs. Robert M., 1957
  - Hargrove, Elizabeth, 1947
  - Harnischfeger, W., 1948
  - Harpprecht, Klaus, 1958-1968
  - Harriman, Mrs. Borden, 1944
  - Harriman, G. Egerton, 1939
  - Harriman, Ambassador W. Averell, 1953-1965
  - Harrington, Miss, 1944
  - Harris, Beulah, 1960
  - Harris, Senator Fred R., 1967-1971
  - Harris, Henry U., 1966
  - Harris, Louis H., 1940
  - Harrison, Mrs., 1950-1951
  - Harrison, Governor Albertis S., Jr., 1965
  - Harrison, Alice F., 1960
  - Harrison, Charles Yale, 1944
  - Hart, Augustus, 1960
  - Hart, Merwin K., 1947-1948
  - Hart, Senator Philip A., 1959-1963
  - Hartig, Count Fred, 1955-1956
  - Hartke, Senator Vance, 1963-1967
  - Hartnett, Father Robert C., 1951-1955
  - Hasbrouck, Jan, 1957
  - Hase, Karl-Guenther von, 1963-1967
  - Hasek, J. K., 1959
  - Haskell, Merwin, 1940
  - Hassel, Kai-Uwe von, 1963
  - Hassenkamp, Gerd B., 1954
  - Hatfield, Governor Mark O., 1959-1961
  - Haught, Robert L., 1965
  - Hauptmann, Jerzy, 1971
  - Hayes, Miss, 1940 (Box 78)
  - Hayman, Peter T., 1963
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1946-1947
  - Hays, Edwin D., 1940
  - Hays, Mortimer, 1943
  - Hays, Representative Wayne L., 1959-1969
  - Hayward, Emeline Place, 1940
  - Hazlitt, Henry, 1944-1946
  - Healy, John D., 1962
  - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1956-1960
  - Heckert, Robert, 1952
  - Heckscher, August, Jr., 1951-1955
  - Heilprin, Frances, 1940
  - Held, Adolph, 1950-1961
  - Heller, Philip A., 1971
  - Hellin, F. P., 1946
  - Hellmold, Heinz, 1950
  - Henderson, Horace D., 1961-1963
  - Henderson, Leon, 1945-1947
  - Henderson, William, 1962-1973
  - Henehan, Anne, 1965-1966
  - Henle, G., 1970
  - Hennis, Wilhelm, 1972
  - Henson, Francis Adams, 1947-1949
  - Herdegen, Gerhard, 1969
  - Hermens, Ferdinand A., 1946-1953
  - Herrarte, Ambassador Alberto, 1959
  - Herrick, Elinore M., 1952-1954
  - Hersey, John, 1960
  - Herter, Christian A., 1948-1966
  - Herwarth, Willy von, 1953-1954
  - Herz, Michael M., 1945
  - Herzberg, Sidney, 1947
  - Hessellund-Jensen, Ambassador Asge, 1958
  - Heymann, Egon, 1959
  - Hibbs, Ben, 1946-1948
  - Hickenlooper, Senator Bourke B., 1947-1960
  - Hickey, Edward J., 1961
  - Hiestand, Representative Edgar W., 1959
  - Hietala, Ester L., 1947
  - Higgins, Marguerite, 1958-1961
  - High, Stanley, 1947
  - Hill, Isabel Preston, 1944
  - Hill, Senator Lister, undated
  - Hillenbrand, Ambassador Martin J., 1962-1974
  - Hillings, Representative Patrick J., 1957
  - Hilpert, W., 1953
  - Hirsch, Felix E., 1952-1972
  - Hirsch, Helmut, 1950-1952
  - Hirschberg, Besse, 1946
  - Hobart, Harold C., 1939 (Box 79)
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1960
  - Hoben, Lindsay, 1958
  - Hochman, Julius, 1947
  - Hochschild, Harold K., 1940
  - Hocker, John Christopher, 1973
  - Hoeffer, Werner, 1963-1967
  - Hoffherr, Fred G., 1943
  - Hoffman, Isidor B., 1946
  - Hoffman, Malvina, 1949
  - Hoffman, Ross J. S., 1946-1947
  - Hoffman, Sal B., 1952-1968
  - Hoffmann, C. Julius, 1958-1972
  - Hoffmann, Oswald C. J., 1953
  - Hogan, Cicero S., 1957
  - Hogan, Rita D., 1950
  - Hogan, Father Walter B., 1956
  - Hoguet, Peter W., 1950
  - Hoguet, Robert Louis, 1945-1947
  - Hohnholz, J., 1967
  - Holborn, Frederick, 1964
  - Holborn, Hajo, 1963-1966
  - Holcomb, George, 1957
  - Holifield, Representative Chet, 1960
  - Holland, Kenneth, 1953-1955
  - Holland, Senator Spessard L., 1959
  - Holmes, Reverend John Haynes, 1946-1947
  - Holmes, William M., 1941
  - Holmes Direct Mail Service, 1955
  - Holt, Cooper T., 1957
  - Hook, Sidney, 1940-1973
  - Hoover, President Herbert, 1944-1960
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1958
  - Hoover, Lyman, 1959
  - Hope, Lord John, 1953
  - Hopkins, Arthur H., 1959
  - Horan, Representative Walt, 1959
  - Horkheimer, Max, 1970
  - Horn, A. B., 1952
  - Horten, Alphons, 1970-1973
  - Horton, Representative Frank, 1965-1967
  - Horvath, George, 1965-1966
  - Horvath, Janos, 1960
  - Hoskins, Harold B., 1940
  - Hosmer, Representative Craig, 1969
  - Hotel Sulgrave, 1946
  - Hottelet, Richard C., 1958-1967
  - Hovde, Bryn J., 1949
  - Hovey, J. Allan, Jr., 1962
  - Howard, J. F., 1958
  - Howard, Jack R., 1947-1959
  - Howard, P. E., 1961
  - Howard, Roy W., 1944
  - Howard, Sidney, 1938
  - Howard, W. J., 1952
  - Howe, H., Jr., 1967
  - Howe, Quincy, 1944-1967
  - Howley, Frank L., 1950-1968
  - Hruby, Reverend Blahoslav, 1969-1971
  - Hruska, Senator Roman L., 1959-1969
  - Hsia, C. L., 1945
  - Hsueh, Y. C., 1957
  - Hubbard, Mayor Orville L., 1970
  - Huber, Captain, 1946
  - Huddleston, Representative George, Jr., 1959
  - Huffman, Mrs. Huston, 1957
  - Huger, Louise P., 1946-1966
  - Hughes, John, 1966
  - Hughes, Mrs. John Chamber, 1957
  - Hughes, Thomas L., 1971
  - Hull, Cordell, 1944
  - Humphrey, Senator Hubert H., 1955-1970 (Box 80)
  - Hunt, Alice, 1947-1949
  - Hunt, Richard M., 1969-1973
  - Hunter, Edward, 1958-1959
  - Hupka, Herbert, 1963
  - Huston, Cloyce K., 1959
  - Hutchison, Harold, 1947
  - Hutten, Baron Friedrich-Karl von, undated
  - Huxley, Michael, 1940
  - Hynning, Clifford J., 1969
  - Hyslop, Beatrice F., 1961
  - Iason, Lawrence, 1940
  - Iddon, Don, 1947
  - Illitch, M. P., 1946
  - Ingersoll, Ralph, 1941-1946
  - International Rescue and Relief Committee, 1946
  - Irvine, Reed J., 1973
  - Irwin, Wallace, Jr., 1955-1961
  - Iselin, Mrs. Oliver, 1946
  - Iselin, Warburton, 1945
  - Ives, Senator Irving M., 1956-1958
  - Ivrakis, Solon, 1948
  - Jackson, C. D., 1956-1961
  - Jackson, Representative Donald L., 1959
  - Jackson, Senator Henry M., 1957-1968
  - Jackson, Kay, 1946
  - Jackson, Percival E., 1939
  - Jacobs, Norman, 1961-1964
  - Jacobsohn, Peter, 1955
  - Jaeger, Richard, 1958-1968
  - Jaegher, R. J. de, 1967
  - Jaenicke, Joachim, 1954
  - Jaeserich, Helmut, 1961-1962
  - Jaffe, Philip, undated
  - Jahn, Hans-Edgar, 1958-1960
  - Jaksch, Wenzel, 1946-1966
  - James, Daniel, 1950-1963
  - James, Edwin L., 1946
  - Janiczek, Ferdinand, 1948
  - Jansen, Thomas, 1973
  - Jarema, Stephen J., 1961
  - Jarmin, Gary L., 1973
  - Javits, Senator Jacob K., 1954-1973
  - Jenlenko, J. F., 1940
  - Jennings, Theodore P., 1970
  - Jessup, John K., 1947-1968
  - Jewish War Veterans, 1950 (Box 81)
  - Joftes, Saul E., 1963
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1946-1949
  - Johnson, Colonel Chester L., 1958
  - Johnson, Clinton, 1953
  - Johnson, Eugene, 1946
  - Johnson, Joseph E., 1958-1960
  - Johnson, Senator Lyndon B., 1960
  - Johnson, Reverend William R., 1946
  - Johnson, Stephen H., 1966
  - Johnston, Eric, 1959-1960
  - Jolis, Albert E., 1959
  - Jonas, Gilbert, 1958-1965
  - Jonas, Pal, 1958
  - Jones, Arthur E., 1965
  - Jones, John Price, 1940-1946
  - Jones, Representative Marvin, undated
  - Jones, Mrs. Robert McKittrick, 1957
  - Jordan, Father Placid, 1962
  - Jordan, Wilbur K., 1949-1953
  - Jordan, William M., 1958
  - Joseph, D. H., 1947
  - Joseph, Franz Martin, 1953-1962
  - Joseph, Nathan, 1940
  - Josselson, M., 1957
  - Josten, J., 1959-1960
  - Joyce, William, 1959
  - Judd, Representative Walter H., 1945-1972
  - Jurgela, Constantine R., 1950
  - Kaghan, Theodore, 1958
  - Kahn, Marcia L., 1952-1973
  - Kaiden, F. G., 1946
  - Kaiser, Herman George, 1972-1973
  - Kalb, Mary, 1965
  - Kallen, Horace N., 1947-1949
  - Kaltenborn, Hans V., 1944-1955
  - Kaltenborn, Olga (Mrs. Hans V.), 1952
  - Kamil, Ambassador Dato Nik Ahmed, 1961
  - Kampelman, Max M., 1955
  - Kanngiesser, H. W., 1960
  - Kaplan, Morris H., 1966
  - Kappel, Albert D., 1963-1965
  - Karelsen, Frank E., Jr., 1940
  - Karp, Basil, 1959
  - Kaskell, Joseph, 1952-1973 (Box 82)
  - Kastner, Alton, 1961-1964
  - Kaszubowski, Joseph H., 1944
  - Katcher, Leo, 1940
  - Katz, Stephen, 1970-1972
  - Kaufman, Mr., 1944
  - Kaufman, George S., 1949
  - Keating, Senator Kenneth B., 1959-1973
  - Keeley, Joseph C., 1956
  - Keenan, Father Charles, 1944-1949
  - Keenan, John C., 1956-1957
  - Keep, Mabel, 1947
  - Kefauver, Senator Estes, 1957-1960
  - Keller, Father James, 1946-1957
  - Keller, Max, 1947
  - Kellerman, Henry J., 1952-1954
  - Kelley, Nicholas, 1947
  - Kellogg, Raymond S., 1949
  - Kelly, Representative Edna F., 1959-1964
  - Kelman, Steven, 1973
  - Kempner, Maximilian W., 1971
  - Kempner, Paul H., 1952
  - Kempton, Murray, 1946-1969
  - Kenna, Richard, 1956
  - Kennan, George F., 1959
  - Kennard, Reverend J. Spencer, Jr., 1946
  - Kennedy, Senator Edward M., 1967-1971
  - Kennedy, James A., 1959-1960
  - Kennedy, President John F., 1956-1962
  - Kennedy, Senator Robert F., 1956-1967
  - Kenney, Don, 1957
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1939
  - Kerekes, Tibor, 1946-1947
  - Kerensky, Alexander, 1949
  - Kern, Harry F., 1950-1953
  - Kernan, Father William C., 1946
  - Kershaw, Anthony, 1959
  - Kersten, Hans Ulrich, 1970
  - Kertzen, Morris N., 1956
  - Kesler, Bruce N., 1969-1973
  - Kidder, Arthur A., Jr., 1957
  - Kieffer, John S., 1940
  - Kiep, Walther Leisler, 1968-1972
  - Kiesinger, Chancellor Kurt Georg, 1966-1970
  - Kikel, John, 1949
  - Killigrew, John W., 1963
  - Kim, Reverend John Starr, 1944
  - King, Governor Bruce, 1973
  - King, Ambassador Charles T. O., 1959
  - King, Edith, 1953
  - King, James E., Jr., 1971
  - King, Robert, 1958
  - King-Hall, Commander Stephen, 1950-1951